- 你好 - 你好
- Hello? - Hello.
- 什么事 - 你是谁
- Uh, yes? - Who is this?
- 你找谁 - 你是谁
- Who are you calling? - Who am I speaking to?
- 你打错了 - 谁啊
- Wrong number. - Who was that?
- 没谁 - 你选好电影了吗
- Oh, nobody. - Did you pick a movie?
选好了 我们看恐怖片《电锯惊魂4》
Yeah, we re gonna go scary: Saw IV.
我在电影院看过了 特烂
Oh, I saw that in theaters. It sucks.
一点都不可怕 特恶心
It's not scary, it's gross.
我痛恨一切变态低俗的玩意
I hate all that torture porn shit.
你还生气了啊
Why, you are really feel.
我喜欢竖锯(《电锯惊魂》主角)
Well, I like Jigsaw.
他杀人很有创意
I think he kills people very creatively.
但她才不在乎谁死了...
But she don't give a shit who dies...
因为死者都大同小异
cos there's no character to fill a man.
只是 尸体肢解 血液喷溅
It's just body parts whipping and blood spewing.
你给谁发信息呢
Who you keep texting?
我在脸谱网(社交网站)的聊友
I have a Facebook stalker.
他不停地给我留言
He keeps leaving me messages.
- 都说些什么 - 说些 你好
- Nah, like what? - Just stuff like: Hey,
怎么样 你很性感 我想杀了你...
what's up? You are hot. I want to kill you...
- 删了他 - 我删了 但他又加进来了
- Well, delete him. - I did it, but he hacked its way back in.
那就举报他
Or report him.
他身材很赞 想看吗
He is really hot, tho. You wanna see?
这是查宁·塔图姆
That's Channing Tatum.
才不是 真的吗
It is not. Is it?
是的 代言阿贝克隆比(美国时装品牌)时的照片
Yeah, from his Abercrombie days.
你被耍了
You were being punk'd.
- 你好 - 你是谁
- Hello? - Who is this?
一个被你搅得更加躁狂的人
The more impatient version of the person you just spoke to.
很抱歉 你不必像个泼妇一样
I am sorry. You don't have to be a bitch about it.
我当然不必 咬我啊
Of course I don't. Eat me.
你敢挂我电话
You hang up on me and I cut
- 我就割断你的脖子 - 谁啊
- thru your neck until I feel bone! - Who is it?
找你的
It's for you.
- 你好 - 你是谁
- Hello? - Who is this?
我是托蒂 你是谁
It's Trudie. Who's this?
我是你死前见到的最后一个人
This is the last person you ever gonna see alive.
- 是恶作剧 挂掉 - 为什么让我接
- It's a prank. Hang up. - Why did you give the phone to me?
- 你有跟踪者啊 - 锁门了没
- You are the one with a stalker. - Are the doors locked?
别大惊小怪
Don't freak out.
别管它
Let it ring.
是那个跟踪者 他说"接电话"
It's from stalker boy. He said "Answer the phone".
听着 这是个玩笑 托蒂
For God's sake, it's a joke, Trudie.
也许是莱克西或凯伦
It's probably Lexie or Karen.
- 你去哪 - 去看前门锁上没
- Where are you going? - To make sure the front door is locked.
- 不 别开门 - 你反应过度了
- No, don't open it. - You're overreacting.
这是个玩笑 托蒂
It's a joke, Trudie, ok?
有人在故弄玄虚
Someone made a dummy profile.
他们只是想吓唬你
They re just trying to scare you.
等等 是谁
Wait. Who is it?
我说 是谁啊 我们报警吧
I said, who is it? Let's call the cops.
"我打赌你不敢开门"
"I dare you to open the door."
不 雪莉 别开 别开 我害怕
No, Sherri, don't. No, don't, I'm scared.
可能是熟人 丽莎 贝莉 韦恩
It could be anyone that we know. Lisa, Bailey, Wayne.
或者是期盼已久的查宁·塔图姆
Or the hoped-for long shot, Channing Tatum.
根本没有人
There is nobody out here.
他说什么
What is it say?
他说:"我不在外面 我就在你旁边"
It says "I'm not outside, I am right beside you. "
托蒂
Trudie!
(刺杀6)
- 开什么玩笑 - 怎么了
- Fucking kidding me? - What?
真他妈愚蠢 太扯淡了
That was so fucking stupid. Pure horse shit.
所谓的身临其境的死亡恐怖
The death of horror right here in front of us!
我吓着了 挺吓人的
I jumped. It scared me.
一个脸谱网杀手吗 你开玩笑吧
A fucking Facebook killer? You re kidding me right?
如果用微博杀手 会更合理
I guess now it would be Twitter. That'd make more sense.
能说会道的高中生坐在一起剖析恐怖片
Under articulate teens sit around and
直到鬼脸把他们一个个杀死
deconstruct horror movies until Ghostface kills them one by one.
注定要死
It's been done to death.
一群有自负的后现代蠢蛋
The whole self-aware post-modern meta-shit.
在1996年就已经被叉死了
Stick a fork in 1996 already.
我喜欢《刺杀》 它们更恐怖
I like the Stab movies. They are scarier.
不像外星人 僵尸或者东方女鬼
It's not aliens or zombies or little Asian ghost girls.
挺真实的
There is something real
一个家伙拿着刀...猛刺
about a guy with a knife who just ... snaps.
- 这真会发生 - 我可做不到
- It can really happen. - I can't do it.
这些人不知道什么时候收手
These people don't know when to stop.
他们反复做着同样的蠢事
They just keep recycling the same shit.
甚至开场 总是有个倒霉的女孩
Even the opening scene, there is always some random
接到电话 然后必然被杀死
girl who gets a call that undoubtedly ends up getting her killed.
一切都在预料之中 没什么悬念
It's all so predictable. There's no element of surprise.
你可以预知一切
You can see everything coming.
这让你意外了吗
Did that surprise you?
- 为什么 - 因为你太啰嗦了
- Why? - Because you talk too much.
现在闭嘴看电影吧
Now shut the fuck up and watch the movie.
(刺杀7)
上帝啊 我超爱这部
Oh my God. I love it.
我看过五遍了 每次都吓到我
I've seen it five times, and it still gets me every time.
开玩笑吧 我真不理解
You re kidding? I don't get it.
就好比电影《阴阳魔界》
Ok, it's like the Twilight Zone.
- 《阴阳魔界》... - 电影套着电影
- Twilight zone... - A movie within a movie.
我明白 但那不合逻辑
I get that. But it's illogical..
如果《刺杀7》的开场是《刺杀6》
It begs the question that if the beginning
那么《刺杀6》的就是《刺杀5》
of Stab 7 is Stab 6 then it's the beginning of Stab 6 Stab 5?
如果这样 《刺杀4》呢
And if so, what is Stab 4 about?
你想多了
You re over thinking it.
是我想多了还是你从没想过
Am I or did you ever make it,
想想吧 我不看这种电影是有原因的
just under think it, there's a reason I don't watch these movies?
真不敢相信你没看过
I can't believe you haven't seen them.
我们可是住在伍兹伯勒
We live in Woodsboro.
和伍兹伯勒没关系吧
It has nothing to do with Woodsboro.
我记得你说过《刺杀》是真事改编的
I thought you said Stab was based on true stories.
前3部是
The first three, the original
以西德尼·普雷斯科特为原型
trilogy is based off of Sidney Prescott.
为此她威胁要起诉他们
But then she threatened to sue them if they
于是他们就开始编故事
used the true story so they just started making stuff up.
在《刺杀5》里还有时空穿越 是至今最差的一部
Stab 5 has time travel, which is by far the worst.
你每年都看不厌吗
And don't you have enough about this story every year?
至少伍兹伯勒是因此而知名的
At least Woodsboro is known for something.
你听见了吗
Did you hear that?
没有 我什么都没听到
Uh, no, I didn't hear anything.
我听到了
I did.
珍妮 别想吓我
Jenny, don't try to scare me.
我没想吓你
I am not trying to scare you.
你老这么做
You do it all the time.
不 我没有
No, I don't.
你去哪
Where are you going?
我说了 我听到有声音
I told you, I heard something.
我知道你是想吓我
I know you re trying to scare me.
我没有
I am not.
是什么
What is it?
我没关房间的窗户
I must have left the window in my room open.
- 能接一下吗 玛妮 - 好
- Could you get that? Marnie? - Yeah.
- 你好 - 你好 你是谁
- Hello? - Hello. Who is this?
玛妮 你是谁
Marnie. Who is this?
我是你死前见到的最后一个人
This is the last person you ever gonna see alive.
什么
What?
- 对不起 我忍不住 - 你这个贱人
- I am sorry. I had to. - You bitch!
- 一点都不好笑 - 有人每年都上当
- So not funny. - Somebody falls for it every year.
我真不明白你为什么以此为乐...
I don't see why you get off on this shi...
玛妮
Marnie?
玛妮 玛妮
Marnie? Marnie?!
演得不错 玛妮
Good one, Marnie.
关了灯 电话扔在地上
Lights out, phone on the floor.
你真应该导演恐怖片
You know, you really should direct horror films.
不管你在哪...
Wherever you are...
我猜猜 你想让我
Lemme guess. You want me to
走过开着的门 然后你突然跳出来
walk by an open door frame so you can pop out, huh?
好吧 时机 时机很完美
Ok. Timing, timing is perfect.
但你的手机没装软件
But you don't have the app on your phone,
你不能模仿鬼脸
so you can't talk like Ghostface.
- 你能吗 - 是的 我能
- Can you? - Yes, I can.
- 你是谁 - 不是软件变声哦
- Who is this? - Not an app.
- 是特雷弗吗 - 我听起来像特雷弗吗
- Is this Trevor? - Do I sound like a Trevor to you?
把我当成导演 你在我的电影里
Think of me as your director. You re in my movie.
你有个有趣的角色 别演砸了
You got a fun part so don't blow it.
- 什么电影 - 玛妮也参演的电影
- What movie? - Same one Marnie's in,
只不过她的戏份结束了
only her part got cut way back.
但是你 这个胸大无脑的金发妞儿
But you, you are the dumb blond with the big tits.
我们在你死前会和你玩个痛快
We'll have some fun with you before you die.
我成绩4分 智商135 混蛋
I have a 4.0 GPA and 135 IQ asshole.
你把玛妮怎么样了
What did you do with Marnie?
她在剪接室的地上
She's on the cutting room floor.
这一点也不好玩
That's not funny.
这不是喜剧片 这是恐怖片
This isn't a comedy, it's a horror film.
有人生 有人死
People live, people die.
你最好开始逃命
And you'd better start running.
玛妮
Marnie?
《惊声尖叫4》
- 你觉得怎么样 - 我猜今天是纪念日吧
- What do you think? - Well, I guess today's the anniversary.
- 孩子们 - 不 我指这个展示
- Kids... - No, I meant the display.
(《冲出黑暗》 "一个幸存者的真实故事" 今日下午一点)
- 很不错 - 我威胁店主
- It's good. - Told the owner
如果你没大卖我就杀了他的猫
I'd kill his cat if you didn't get a ring.
很好...
Nice...
(警长)
限速25码
Woah, 25 to stay alive!
该死 抱歉长官
Shit! Sorry Sheriff!
科比...
Kirby...
你上车前
Ehi, before you get in the car,
先保证不会杀了我
you have to promise not to kill me.
为什么 你做了什么
Why? What did you do?
特雷弗昨晚给我打电话了
Trevor called me last night.
他为什么给你打电话
Why is he calling you?
因为你不接他的电话
Because you won't take his calls,
他知道咱俩是好姐妹 他想知道
he knows I have your ear and he wants to know.
- 知道什么 - 知道你有多生气
- Know what? - How upset you are.
- 可以先不聊这个吗 - 好 好
- Can we just not talk about this? - Fine, fine.
特雷弗昨晚给我打电话了
So, Trevor called me last night.
他也给你打了
He called you too?
他担心你表姐的到来
He's afraid your cousin coming to Woodsboro
会让你无暇考虑他的歉意
is distracting you from knowing how sorry he really is.
- 真是别出心裁 - 上帝啊...
- Well, that's inventive. - God...
顺便问一句 你看《死神》了吗
Oh, by the way, have you seen the Grim Reaper?
那《死亡天使》呢
Angel of Death?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
你表姐 巡回签售的最后一站
Your cousin. Last stop in a book tour,
开始新生活的第一站
first stop in a road to a new life.
太激动人心了 她使我爱上了恐怖片
It's very dramatic. She's the reason why I love horror movies.
听到这话她肯定特开心
I'm sure she'd love to hear that.
我不见得了解她
If I knew her which, I don't really.
她走到哪里都会有人死
Well, wherever she went, peple died.
死的总是别人 永远不是她
Other people. It was never her.
我是说 她不应该叫《刺杀》
I mean, Stab is the wrong franchise for her,
应该叫《死神来了》
it should be Final Destination.
珍妮·兰德尔为什么要给我打电话
And why is Jenny Randall calling me?
- 我受不了珍妮·兰德尔 - 你好
- I cannot stand Jenny Randall... - Hello?
- 吉尔 - 为什么
- Oh, Jill... - Why?
珍妮 是你吗
Shh...Jenny, is this you?
你最喜欢的恐怖片是哪部
What's your favorite scary movie?
- 你是谁 - 她想干嘛
- Ok, who is this? - What does she want?
- 我说 你是谁 - 我在问你
- I said, who is this? - I asked you a question.
你最喜欢的恐怖电影是哪部
What's your favorite scary movie?
我挂了
I'm hanging up.
真是新奇
Wow, that was original.
我今早也接到一个玛妮和卡尼式的电话
I got a call like that this morning from Marnie and Carnie.
- 什么 - 小心
- What? - Watch out!
- 开得真有水平 混蛋 - 没事了...
- Nice proof asshole! - Ok...
- 你应该看标志停车 - 抱歉...
- You should really stop at sign. - Sorry...
就像《死亡天使》
Angel of Death.
市长要求午餐前摘下这些
Mayor wants these down before lunch.
就剩二十五个了
Only 25 more to go.
- 早 警长 - 早 副警长 乔
- Morning Sheriff. - Morning Deputy. Joe.
早 长官
Morning Sheriff.
看起来庆典开始了
Looks like the celebration's begun.
可能是高中生干的
High School kids probably.
是啊 一代人的悲剧成了下代人的笑柄
Yeah. One generation's tragedy is the next one's joke.
抱歉你老被这个纠缠
Sorry you can never get away from this.
真希望你当时处理那些犯罪的时候
You know, I wish I had been old enough
我已经能够参与办案了
to be part of the Forest when you were solving those crimes.
那些紧张的调查很能巩固关系
It's those intense investigations that really bond relationships.
- 是啊 - 加尔怎么样
- Yeah. - How's Gale by the way?
加尔很好 她在写作...小说
Gale's good. She's writing...fiction.
我做了柠檬方蛋糕 在我车里
Hey I made some lemon squares, they're in my car.
谢谢副长官 不必了 谢谢
Thanks Deputy, but no, thanks.
长官 吃我的柠檬方蛋糕
Sheriff, you're not cheating
不算是背叛老婆
on your wife if you eat my lemon square.
是啊 但不利于减肥
Yeah, but I would be cheating on the diet.
瑞利长官 听到吗 瑞利长官
Sheriff Riley! Come in! Sheriff Riley!
我是瑞利长官 请讲
This is Sheriff Riley, go ahead.
你得马上来兰德尔家
You gotta get over to the Randall house right away.
很糟糕 长官 非常糟糕
It's bad Sheriff, real bad.
书名《冲出黑暗》的作者
The book is "Out of Darkness" and
西德尼·普雷斯科特今天和我们聚在这里
its author Sidney Prescott is here with us today.
七部《刺杀》电影都取材于
Have the 7 Stab movies all based on
加尔·威瑟斯写的关于你的书
Gale Weathers' books about you
是否让你更难前行
made it even harder to go on?
我并不怪加尔 都过去了
I don't blame Gale, that's in the past.
我一直都在当受害人
Now if I was a victim for too long,
现在是重塑自我的时候了
it was up to me to reinvent myself.
所以我写了这本书
That's why I wrote this book.
注意了 西德尼·普雷斯科特
Sidney Prescott, everybody.
她的书好评如潮 名为《冲出黑暗》
And rave reviews for her book, "Out of Darkness".
好了 加尔 开工 重塑自我吧
Allright Gale, let's do it. Let's reinvent myself.
只是 我他妈的
Except, I have no fucking
一点灵感都没有
idea what to write!
(伍兹伯勒高中)
- 新的好用吗 - 那是2.0的升级版本
- How's that new? - That's the 2.0 upgrade version.
我应用自如啊 伙计
I am totally mobile, man.
很好
Nice.
这是罗比·默塞尔的《嘿咻卡》
Ouh, this is Hall Pass with Robbie Mercer,
这位是甜美少女奥利维亚
here with the luscious Olivia
"别看我的咪咪 我有思想"的莫里斯
"Don't look at my tits, I have a mind" Morris.
以下是我的伍兹伯勒化妆舞会
Here is my Woodsboro masquerade
纪念日的问题:你最喜欢的恐怖片是什么
anniversary question: What is your favorite scary movie?
你就会这些吗 一些没水平的蠢问题
Is that all you got? Some stupid douche question?
是啊 你从哪听来的
Yeah, where did you hear that anyway?
是《刺杀1》中的一句台词 查理
It's a line from Stab 1. Hey Charlie.
你很有型 科比
You are a genre nut Kirby,
你最喜欢的恐怖电影是什么
What's your favorite scary movie?
是《小鹿斑比》
Bambi.
- 笨蛋 - 怎么了
- Dork. - What?
很有趣 科比
That's...funny, Kirby.
完全无视你的存在
Completely unaware you exist.
不 伙计 她想要我
No, man, she wants me.
天方夜潭 是吗 混蛋
Yeah, I wish, right? Asshole.
- 我觉得查理喜欢你 - 我也喜欢他
- I think Charlie likes you. - And I like him.
嘲笑他 折磨他 让他难为情
To tease, to torment, to make him squirm.
比这糟糕 相信我
You could do a lot worse, trust me.
你好 特雷弗 再见 特雷弗
Oh, hi Trevor. Bye Trevor.
我们能谈谈吗
Can we talk?
这里有人很关心你
Somebody cares about you over here you know?
有人曾让你非常幸福
Someone who made you really happy once.
有人永远都不会让你离开
Someone who never should have let you go.
你接了个电话 就让她走...
When you are done with a phone call, you let someone go...
你送某人去机场 你让他们走...
When you take someone to the airport, you let them go...
当你告诉某人你爱她
When you tell someone you love her,
她为你付出了一切
and she gives you everything,
你却和别人约会...
and then you go out with someone else...
那不是让她走
that is not letting her go,
而是甩了她 那是背叛
that is dumping her. Ok? That's betrayal.
特雷弗·谢尔登拒绝
Trevor Sheldon denied
与罗比·默塞尔上《嘿咻卡》
live on Hall Pass with Robbie Mercer.
你最喜欢的恐怖电影是什么 伙计
What is your favorite scary movie, man?
我演给你看
I'll show you.
我开始相信这就是我
Now I began to believe myself that that was all I was,
一个受害者 对此我无法接受...
a victim. And that was unacceptable to me...
因此 我坐下来开始写
So, I sat down and began
一个新形象 一个自己的形象
to write a new role that would be my own.
一个女人走出恐惧的阴影
A role for a woman who could leave
走向光明的角色
the walls of fear behind and step out into the sunlight.
那就是《冲出黑暗》
Out of Darkness.
- 谢谢 - 好了 我们马上开始签售
- Thank you. - Ok, we're gonna start the book signing in a sec,
欲购从速哦
so buy your copies while they last.
祝福你们 女士
May you ladies.
是《纽约时报》的畅销书 好评如潮...
New York Times best seller. Rave reviews...
加尔 真高兴你能来
Gale...I am glad you came.
祝贺你 西德尼
Congratulations, Sidney.
我还没机会读 但是...
I haven't had a chance to read it yet, but...
你可以拿一本
Well, you can get one.
杜威
Dewey! Ehi!
西德尼 加尔 你说中了
Hey, Sidney. Gale, you made it.
发生什么事了 杜威
What's going on, Dewey?
西德 很抱歉 我有事...非常抱歉
Hey, Sid, I am sorry. I gotta do something...I am really sorry.
抱歉 耽误大家一分钟
Excuse me. This will only take a minute.
我要你们待在原地 保持安静
I need you all to stay where you are and remain silent.
不许走 长官说过了 谢谢
Nobody leaves, you heard the Sheriff, thanks you.
就不能等四十五分钟吗 我正在主持活动
Can't this wait 45, I am running an event here.
女士 现在警察执行公务
M'am this is a police event now.
发生什么事了
What's going on?
加尔 这是警察的事
Gale, this is police business.
请你让我们来处理这事
If you could just let us handle this.
我在和我丈夫讲话 朱迪副长官
I am talking to my husband, Deputy Judy.
听着 我们相信
Listen. There's a phone we believe
有一部手机被带离了犯罪现场
may have been taken from the scene of a crime.
希克斯副长官追踪到它在这里
Deputy Hicks has traced its location back to these coordinates.
- 其它的还未知 - 我不能知道吗
- The rest is "Need to know". - And I am not "Need to know"?
长官 声音在外面
Sheriff! Ringing out here!
在那
There.
- 在后备箱里 - 没错
- It's coming from the trunk. - Yeah.
- 杜威... - 大家往后站
- Dewey... - They need everyone to stay back.
现在不是时候 西德
Not now, Sid.
这是我租的车
It's my rental.
- 该死 - 现在这里是犯罪现场
- Damn. - It's now official crime scene.
封锁现场
Let's lock it down.
- 犯罪现场 - 把他带出去
- Crime scene. - Detach him right out of here.
- 大家撤退 - 给我照相机 - 往后站
- Everybody back. - Give me that camera. - Stand back.
- 给我照相机 - 往后站
- Give me that camera. - Stand back.
请告诉我这是恶作剧 杜威.
Please tell me this is a prank, Dewey.
恐怕不是 西德 来吧
I am afraid not, Sid. Come on.
安布尔 你绝对不相信...
Amber, you're not gonna believe this...
靠后 加尔 加尔
Stand back, Gale. Gale.
只是看看而已
Just wanna see.
周二前交作文"为什么伍兹伯勒是最..."
Ok, essays are due Tuesday, "Why Woodsboro is the best..."
上课关机 这是规矩
Anything with an on-off swith should be off, that's the rule.
有人说说发生什么了吗
Somebody wanna share?
珍妮·兰德尔和玛妮·库铂
Jenny Randall and Marnie Cooper
- 昨晚被杀害了 - 什么
- were murdered last night. - What?
- 什么 - 遇刺身亡
- What? - Stabbed to death.
- 你最喜欢的恐怖片是什么 - 闭嘴
- What's your favorite scary movie? - Shut up!
- 说到周二 肯定上不了课了 - 真快
- Y'all Tuesday, class is not hold then - That was fast.
本周是
This week marks the
声名狼籍的伍兹伯勒杀手周年纪念日
anniversary of the infamous Woodsboro murders.
当地著名受害人西德尼·普雷斯科特
Two girls killed the exact day local celebrity
返乡当天 两名女孩被杀
victim Sidney Prescott chose to return to her hometown.
这事好像来自
It could be something right out of
加尔·威瑟斯的畅销书
a Gale Weathers' best seller.
她现在在哪呢
And where is she now?
生活在伍兹伯勒
Well, living right here in Woodsboro,
因为她是长官杜威·瑞利的妻子
cos she's the wife of Sheriff Dewey Riley...
- 瑞利夫人 - 霍斯
- Mrs Riley - Hoss.
- 长官夫人 - 铂金斯
- First Lady. - Perkins.
抱歉 加尔 他正在面谈
Excuse me, Gale. He's conducting an interview.
很好 我喜欢面谈
Great! I love interviews.
你得等着 加尔
You have to wait, Gale.
抱歉 你不能进去
Sorry, can't let you in there.
你想怎样 抓我吗 朱迪副长官
What are you gonna do? Arrest me, Deputy Judy?
只要你真这样做了
If it comes to it.
公众干扰警方调查
Civilian interference with a police investigation
造成许多法律问题
poses many a problem in a court of law.
行 你听着 朱迪
Ok. Listen to me Judy.
我不介意你和我丈夫共事
I don't mind that you re working with my hudband,
或者做点心给他吃
or that you're even baking those little treats, as you do.
但如果你要像他那样行事
But if you're gonna start acting like him,
你得贴个胡子 因为你很搞笑
you gotta put a mustache on, cos you sound ridiculous.
加尔
Gale.
- 朱迪 - 加尔
- Judy. - Gale!
副长官 加尔 冷静点
Deputy. Gale. Calm please.
西德尼 如果你不介意等一等
Sidney, if you don't mind giving us a minute.
- 西德 - 你好 加尔
- Sid. - Hi, Gale.
杜威 你可以向这位贝蒂妙厨
Dewey, would you please explain to Betty Crocker
解释我有权造访警局吗
that I have every right to be here?
如果伍兹伯勒又出现谋杀...
If there's been another murder in Woodsboro obviusly....
消息还没公开
That is not public information.
网上都传开了 杜威
It is all over the Internet, Dewey.
真的吗
It is?
显然 我是最后一个知道的了
Yes, the whole world knows about it before me.
她想介入调查 警长
She wants to be a part of the investigation, Sheriff.
行 等一下
Ok. Hang on. Uhm, are you
你知道我写过一本书是关于这桩案件的吗
familiar with the phrase "I wrote a book on this" ?
加尔 恕我直言
Gale, with all due respect,
我不觉得这有相关性...
I don't see how that pertains to...
因为我写过关于这起案件的书
Because I wrote the book on this.
是《伍兹伯勒谋杀案》作者 加尔·威瑟斯
"The Woodsboro murders" by Gale Weathers.
但是你不再是记者了 加尔
But you re not a reporter anymore, Gale.
就算你是...
And even if you were...
不要把我当成媒体
Don't treat me like I'm the media.
我当时帮忙破案了
I helped solve these things.
足足3次 还记得吗
3 times, remember?
你和我一起的
You and me, together.
- 但我现在是警长了 加尔 - 又如何
- But I am the Sheriff now, Gale. - Right?
你是不打算让我帮忙了吗
What, you re not gonna help you with this?
我不可以这样做
I can't.
行 那我自己干
All right then, I am going rogue.
我一直擅长此事 杜威
This is what I am good at, Dewey.
我知道该怎么做
This is what I know how to do.
你的柠檬方蛋糕跟屁股一个味道
Your lemon squares taste like ass.
- 不是 很好吃 - 谢谢你 长官
- They don't. They really don't. - Thank you, Sir.
- 警长 - 什么事
- Sheriff. - Yeah?
几个高中学生来报案
We got a couple high school kids in here.
其中两个说今天早上
Two of them, they say they got threatening
接到从受害人电话打来的威胁电话
phone calls this morning from the victims' phones.
他们的名字是
Names are
奥利维亚·莫里斯和吉尔·罗伯茨
Olivia Morris and Jill Roberts.
她是西德的表妹 该死的
That's Sid's cousin. Damn.
- 她们在这里 警长 - 吉尔
- Right in here, Sheriff. - Hey, Jill.
- 西德尼 你好 - 你好
- Sidney. Hi. - Hi.
见到你真好 即使在这种情况下
It's nice to see you, even under the circumstances.
- 还好吗 - 还行
- You ok? - Yeah.
是你们其中两个接到电话吗
So two of you got phone calls?
是 我们两个
Yeah, us two.
你最喜欢的恐怖片是哪部
"What's your favorite scary movie?"
是那个杀手的声音 《刺杀》里的
It was the killer's voice. From Stab.
来自 你明白的 来自你的生活
From, I mean you know, from your life.
我是科比 她们的朋友
I am Kirby, by the way. I am their friend.
- 杀手没打电话给你吗 - 没有
- And the killer didn't call you? - No.
这会...这会很糟糕吗
This is...this is a bad thing?
是不是意味着我没她们活得长
Does that mean that I am not gonna live as long as these two?
不是 或许 当然不是
No...Maybe. Of course not.
不过要小心
Just...just be careful.
我的天 听见了吗 我是下个目标
Oh my God, did you hear that? I am gonna be next!
杜威 我不该来这 我该离开
Dewey, I shouldn't be here. I should leave town.
恐怕不行 西德尼
I am afraid that's not really possible, Sidney.
不是说你跟此案有关
Look, nobody thinks you're involved
但任何人都有嫌疑 抱歉
but everyone's a suspect. I am sorry.
况且在你的车里发现的证据
And there was evidence in your car
证明杀手与你有关
connecting the killer to you.
你有可能是重要证人
You may be a material witness.
所以 你会受到
So, you know, you'll have
警方二十四小时的监视
24 hour police surveillance.
那倒是让人安心
That's comforting.
我是丽贝卡 我的天 亨利
It's Rebecca. Oh my fucking God, Henry.
真的 两个女孩被杀 大赚一笔了
Yes! It's true. Two girls butchered. Pay day.
我对伍兹伯勒毫无好感
I was so not feeling Woodsboro.
是不是像瘸腿公关 对吧
Was like LAME PR, am I right?
正振奋了 绝好的点子
Well, fuck me wow! Best idea ever.
亨利 回头打给你
Henry, I'll call you back.
不好意思 我实在难以自禁
Excuse me. I have to geek out.
之前没有机会跟你说话
I hadn't got a chance to say something earlier,
见到你真荣幸
but it's suck an honor to meet you.
- 谢谢 - 我是丽贝卡·沃尔特斯
- Thank you. - Rebecca Walters.
你好
Hi.
我小时候到处都是加尔·威瑟斯的精彩故事
When I was a kid it was all about top story with Gale Weathers.
你就是我的九十年代
You were my 90s!
我现在是加尔·瑞利了
Well, it's Gale Riley now.
你为爱情放弃了事业 我知道
You gave it all for love, I know that.
你和杜威结婚多久了
How long have you and Dewey been married?
- 十年 - 跟你《刺杀3》里的角色一样
- Ten years. - Oh, just like your characters in Stab 3. Wow!
我没有恶意 只是貌似
I didn't mean "Bad wow", it's just, it always
恐怖片比现实里有更多浪漫
seemed like more of a horror movie romance than a real one
因为是电影 而现实中不会存在
because it was a movie, and in real life it should never be.
挖个洞 在这里爬出来 无论如何
Dug a hole. Climbing out, here. So anyway,
放弃职业生涯的勇气实在让人佩服
Kudos on being brave enough to drop off the professional map.
是否打算东山再起呢
Any plans on revitalizing your tarnished brand?
听着 我将在两秒内
Listen, in about 2 seconds I am
把你的脸打得闪闪亮
gonna revitalize your face... with my tarnished brand.
不减当年
I still got it.
有点意思
Uhm, tasty.
她真漂亮
She's so pretty.
当一想到她的遭遇
When you think about what she survived,
我猜她身上到处是伤痕
she must have scars everywhere.
小声点 拜托
Shhhh, Come on.
她母亲是我姐姐 我也有伤痕
Her mom is my sister. I have scars too.
从没人问起过我的伤痕
None ever asks me about my scars.
对不起 罗伯茨太太
I am sorry Mrs Roberts.
她是指美好的伤痕 妈妈
She means nice scars, mom.
没事 没关系
Oh, well. Fine.
你过得好吗 加尔呢
How are you? How's Gale?
我很好 但是加尔
I am alright. But Gale,
就比较委屈了
it's been hard on her.
小城镇 和来自小城镇的丈夫
Small town. Small town husband.
没什么好写的
Not much to write about.
你们两个还好吗
You two ok?
曾经在哪里看到过的
Well, I read somewhere once
"当你觉得事情不能再糟糕了
"Just when you think things can't get any worse,
有时就真的不会了...有时 还会变好"
sometimes they don't...sometimes, they get better".
西德尼·普雷斯科特的《走出黑暗》220页
Out of Darkness by Sidney Prescott, page 220.
我要走了
Gotta get going.
见到你真好 杜威
It's nice to see you, Dewey.
我们一起克服了很多
Been through a lot together.
这次也一样
We'll get through this too, ok?
我走了
I'll go.
没事 别紧张 别紧张 是我
Be good. It's ok. Relax, relax. It's just me.
你在这里干什么
What the hell are you doing here?
外面有警察守着
There are cops right out front.
他们不是忍者的对手 宝贝
No match for the ninja, baby.
你在西德尼·普雷斯科特的房子干什么
Anyway, what are you doing in the house of Sidney Prescott?
感觉在跟杰弗里·达默玩顶级厨师游戏(1994年美国杀人犯)
I mean, that's like being on Top Chef with Jeffrey Dahmer.
拜托你别靠近窗户
Can you please get away from the window?
你在这里不合适 再也不了
You've no right to be in here. Not anymore.
少安毋躁 我听说
Hang on. I heard
你接到杀手的电话 真的吗
you got a phone call from the killer. Is that true?
跟你有什么关系
And you care?
你不觉得有我在身边会安全得多吗
Don't you think it'd be a lot safer with me around?
我不相信你 特雷弗
I don't trust you, Trevor.
我必须让你相信我 对吗
I am just gonna have to make sure that you do. Alright?
抱歉 我不知道...
Oh, sorry, I didn't...
没事 他正要走 他是我前任男友
No, he's just leaving. It's...it's my ex.
唯一一任
The one and only.
见到你感觉很酷...正式地
It's cool to meet you...officially.
我一直想买一本你的书 但...
I keep meaning to pick up a copy of your book, but...
你真人更娇小
You're smaller in person.
- 怎么了 - 没什么
- What? - Nothing,
只是你...让我想起了自己
you just...you remind me of me.
- 记得锁好窗户 - 好的 晚安
- Lock your window, ok? - Yeah, goodnight.
晚安
Night.
抱歉吓到你了
Sorry about that.
在走之前巡视一遍
Just making my rounds before taking off.
好极 谢谢
Great, thanks.
- 你不记得我了吗 - 什么
- You don't remember me, do you? - Sorry?
我们一起上的高中 记得朱迪·希克斯吗
We went to High School together. Judy Hicks?
我们在同一个课室 以及剧社
We had the same Homeroom in. Drama club too.
一起演过《小飞侠》
We were in Peter Pan together.
我演其中一个迷失少年
I played a Lost Boy.
你是...泰格·莉莉
You were... Tiger Lily.
抱歉 时间太久远了
I am sorry, it was a long time ago.
没关系
It's ok.
以前发生的事情实在太多
You had a lot of stuff going on back then.
很高兴再见到你 朱迪
Well, it's nice to see you again, Judy.
我也是
You too.
楼上一切正常吧
Everything ok upstairs?
你应该在前门外待着 铂金斯
You're supposed to be out front, Perkins.
4字母单词代表...勇气
4 letter word for...courage?
胆量
Guts.
那是奥利维亚·莫里斯 住在隔壁
It's Olivia Morris, she lives next door.
她在名单上
She's on the list.
要是她住在我隔壁就好了
She can live next door to me.
说认真地 玛丽 我警告你
Now seriously, Mary. I am warning you, ok?
我要动手了 我说真的
I am gonna have to get physical. I mean it.
真的 他妈的滚开
This is it! Just fuck off!
(奥利维亚)
- 你好 - 你们在做什么
- Hello? - What are you guys up to?
我们在看《僵尸肖恩》
Uhm, we re watching Shaun of the Dead.
知不知道你们家外面车里有两只僵尸
You know there's two zombies sitting outside your house in a car?
是 他们是警察 你要过来吗
Yeah, they are cops. You wanna come up?
"死亡天使"走了吗
Angel of Death leave?
没 她住客房
No, she's in the guest room.
算了 隔壁已经够近的了
Forget it. Next door is close enough.
- 你妈在家吗 - 在她男朋友那里
- Your mom home? - She's at her boyfriend's.
今晚这里更恐怖了
It's creepier in here tonight.
僵尸还在车里
No, the zombies are still in their car,
所以没问题
so you should be alright.
- 明天打电话给我 - 好
- Call me tomorrow, ok? - Right.
- 她要过来吗 - 她害怕"死亡之神"
- She wanna come up? - She fears the Reaper.
看我的
Watch this.
谁
Who's speaking?
你最喜欢的恐怖片是哪部 奥利维亚
What's your favorite scary movie, Olivia?
这是我听过最差的模仿 吉尔
It's the worst imitation I've ever heard, Jill.
说起《刺杀》 你知道刺杀之夜在哪举行吗
Speaking of Stab, you heard where the Stab-a-thon's gonna be at?
没 跟我没关系 反正我妈不让我去
No. It doesn't matter to me anyways, mom doesn't let me go.
特雷弗打来的 让我来摆平吧
It's Trevor, I'll handle this.
特雷弗又打来了
Trevor is calling...again.
- 你想怎样 - 我要跟吉尔说话
- What do you want? - I wanna talk to Jill.
我是科比 抱歉 特雷弗
Uhm, no it's Kirby. Sorry, Trevor,
吉尔在清理她前任的那些通话记录
Jill is screening her calls from all past relationships.
你们那边在干什么
What's going on over there?
等一下 他说什么了
Hang on one sec. What is he saying?
我不是特雷弗
I am not Trevor.
什么 我根本听不清 特雷弗
What? I can barely hear you, Trevor.
我不是特雷弗
This isn't Trevor.
好吧 那你为什么有他的电话
Oh, alright. Then why do you have his phone?
不管你是谁
Whoever this is.
- 他在假装鬼脸 - 诡异的很
- He's trying to do Ghostface. - He's being weird.
我想跟吉尔说话
I wanna talk to Jill.
她不想跟你说话
Ok, well, she doesn't want to talk to you.
来吧 鬼脸先生 跟我说吧
Come on, Mr Ghostface, whisper to me.
不是应该问我一个问题吗
Aren't you supposed to ask me a question?
- 好的 电影好看吗 - 什么电影
- Alright. How's the movie? - What movie?
- 《僵尸肖恩》 - 你怎么知道的
- Shaun of the Dead. - How did you know that?
因为我在衣柜里
Because I'm standing in the closet.
闭嘴 不可能
Stop, you're not.
- 怎么了 - 特雷弗怪怪的
- What's going on? - Trevor is being weird.
- 我不知道是不是他 - 什么
- I mean, if it is him, I don't know. - What?
我他妈不是特雷弗
This is not fucking Trevor!
那你到底他妈的是谁
Well, then who the fuck are you?
打开衣柜
Open the closet door.
你知道房子周围都是警察吧
You do know there are cops all over this house?
我相信自己有时间把某人开膛破肚
I think that I have just enough time to slice someone open.
我来跟他说
I'll talk to him.
你们那边怎么了
What's going on over there, you guys?
我也不知道 科比
Sorry, I don't know. Kirby?
科比
Kirby.
来吧 打开
Come on, do it.
- 你不可能在里面 - 你自己看吧
- There is no way you re in there. - See for yourself.
科比 求你了 告诉我
Kirby? Kirby, come on, talk to me.
一点不好玩 科比
This isn't funny! Kirby!
骗子 我看过了
Liar. I am over this.
我可没说在你的衣柜里
I never said I was in your closet.
我的天
Oh my God!
- 奥利维亚 - 我的天
- Olivia! - Oh my God!
救命 他在我家
Help, in my house!
不
No!
不 不
No. No!
- 霍斯 - 奥利维亚
- Hoss! - Olivia!
铂金斯
Perkins!
狗屎
Shit.
说话
What?
欢迎回家 西德尼 这只是前奏
Welcome home Sidney. Preview of coming events.
怎么不直接冲我来
Why don't you come for me?
你以为自己说了算吗
You got the balls for that?
可怜的西德尼 你以为这全是因为你吗
Oh, poor Sidney. You think this is all about you?
你以为你还是明星吗
You think you're still the star.
这不是他妈的电影
This isn't a fucking movie!
- 会的 - 他们都是无辜的
- It will be. - These are innocent people.
少废话了
Spare me the lecture!
你因为这些鲜血名利双收
You've done very well by all this blood shed, haven't you?
被你遗忘的小镇呢
How about the town you left behind?
我已经为你设计好了
I've got plans for you.
我要把你的眼皮撕成两半
I am gonna slit your eyelids in half
那样你就能亲眼看着我刺穿你的脸
so you don't blink when I stab you in the face.
我要你几时死就几时死 西德尼
You'll die when I want you to, Sidney.
一刻也不差 到那时有你受的
Not a moment before. Until then, you're going to suffer.
- 西德尼 - 吉尔 别进来
- Sidney! - Jill? Stay right there.
- 她是... - 不要看
- Is she... - Do not look, ok?
她说你是死亡天使
She said you were the Angel of Death.
当心
Look out!
- 过来看 那边 - 他在这里面
- Come look. Look over there. - He's in here.
- 人呢 - 他刚刚在这...
- Where is he? - He was...
你那边怎么样
What's your status?
- 吉尔 - 不要
- Jill? - Don't.
怎么了 我的天 吉尔
What happened? Oh my God, Jill.
我的天 宝贝 来
Jesus. Baby, baby. Come here.
来 我们走 我们走 让我照顾你
Come on, let's go, let's go. Let's get care of you, right?
吉尔 我的天 你没事吧
Jill? Oh my God. Are you ok?
扶我一下
Give me a hand.
压住伤口
Keep your pressure on it.
房子后面有人
There's somebody back there.
- 叫他过来 - 好的
- Call it in. - Right.
你还好吗
Hey, are you ok?
你该去楼上处理下
You should look upstairs.
我们各个角落都搜查一下
Let's get the corners and rub around these.
还以为已经了结了呢
Thought this was over!
都是你的错 西德尼
It's all your fault, Sidney.
跟你妈妈一样是扫帚星
Just like her mother!
抱歉我刚刚说了过分的话
I am sorry of what I said.
- 要去看看伤口吧 - 是的
- Shouldn't you get that looked at? - Yeah.
到底发生了什么事
What the hell happened?
之前 我看见他往那边院子跑了
Ok, I saw him going to that yard,
就在前面两座房子
two houses down, right before.
- 我绕过去想截住他 - 然后呢
- And I circled around to cut him off. - And?
然后我就看见霍斯从另一个方向过来
And I met Hoss coming from the other direction.
不 他一定折回去了 跟鬼一样
No, he must have circled back around somehow. He's like a ghost.
- 长官 对不起 - 我们感觉很糟糕
- Chief, we're sorry. - We feel terrible.
好吧 先回去吧
Alright. Get out here.
这里是罗比·默塞尔主播的《嘿咻卡》
This is Hall Pass with Robbie Mercer
深夜现场网络直播
webcasting live in our darkest hour.
作为纪念日的一天
What began as a day of remembrance,
最终以连环谋杀收场
has ended with a serial murder.
这个我泡不上的妞 死了
who officially would never go out with me, is dead.
珍妮·兰德尔和玛妮·库铂也惨遭毒手
So is Jenny Randall and Marnie Cooper.
本地的传奇 《刺杀》系列电影
Our local legacy, the Stab movies,
正在变成现实
is coming to life.
抱歉 你们在用这个东西录像吗
Excuse me, are you recording with that thing?
会上传到我的视频博客
My video blog upload.
他正在网络广播
He's webcasting right now.
介意关掉它吗
Mind turning it off?
一所小破学校 上不了台面
A little old school, off the record?
不能关掉 听众听着呢
Can't. Owe it to my audience.
- 给我马上关掉 - 好吧...
- Turn the fucking thing off. - Ok...
就是你们两个
So, you two are the boys
在伍兹伯勒高中搞电影俱乐部吧
who run the movie club at Woodsboro High, huh?
查理牵头的
Oh, Charlie rents it.
我只是副手 他需要个得力助手
I'm just VP, in case he takes a bullet.
我们叫放映俱乐部
It's called Cinema Club.
想必你对学校里的电影迷们
So you must have a very unique insight
有相当独特的洞察力了
into the movie buffs at your school?
或许
Maybe.
我们联手捉拿杀手 如何
What if we could catch the killer, by working together?
两代新锐新闻工作者
Two generations of cutting edge journalists
共同为媒体事业献出热情
intertwining our passions for media.
- 你应该说什么呢 - 说我爱你吗
- What would you say? - I love you?
非常好
Very good.
那你们提供我一些
Now, you give me your expertise
伍兹伯勒高中变态血案的专业见解
on the gore geek scene at Woodsboro High
或者我可以给予一定回报
and maybe I give you something in return
例如 名人到访你们的放映俱乐部...
Say, a celebrity visit to your Cinema Club...
比如我
by me?
西德尼行吗
What about Sidney?
想请西德尼对吧
你认识她 对吧
Hey, you know her, right?
我是说 你和她是朋友吧
I mean you're friends with her?
无意冒犯 但俱乐部会轰动的
No offense but, that'd be a big deal for some of the club.
西德尼·普雷斯科特到访 她可是个明星
A visit from Sidney Prescott, I mean, she's the star.
如果我是罗琳 那她就是丹尼尔·雷德克里夫
Uh, yes she's Daniel Radcliffe to my J.K. Rowling.
你的书拍成过电影吗
When was the bookshelf in the box office?
没有
Never.
没有骨折 应该没有大碍
There's no broken bones. I think you'll be fine.
只需要休养几个星期
Maybe just take a couple weeks off.
西德尼 长话短说
So, Sidney...Uh, ouh. Anyway, long story short ,
瑞德姆想跟你续签三本书 立刻
Random wants to lock you into 3 more books, now.
看见合同里的空行了吗
See the blank line in your contract?
在那里签名就行了
You can name your phrase.
你一旦洗脱嫌疑
And as soon as you're clear in this investigation,
我们就马上飞去纽约
we're on the next plane to New York.
我约了《今日新闻》《观点》
I booked Today, The View,
南茜·格蕾丝 《音乐电视新闻》
Nancy Grace, mTV News.
抱歉 我...我可以问个问题吗
Excuse me, can I...can I ask you a question?
你读过我的书吗
Did you read my book?
我本来打算等电影版
Thought I'd wait for the movie.
巡回签售到此结束
Book tour is over.
西德尼 接受你的处境吧
Sidney. Accept your situation.
你是个受害者 一直都是
You're a victim, for life.
那就拥抱它 利用它吧
So, embrace it, use it.
我知道你在乎你的读者
I know you care about your readers.
那些失败者需要
All those little down-trodden fucks that just need
看到前方的一丝光明
a light at the end of their tunnels
才不至于绝望
so they don't jump off a bridge.
以这次为契机
And a lucky break like this?
销售量能至少翻个倍
I am talking a 100 percent increase in sales, minimum.
可能会又有一百万人
That's maybe a million more people
受到你的鼓舞
getting your message
而你将会收到更多的报酬 双赢
and you get a ton more checks. Win-win.
- 我不再需要你了 - 西德尼
- I won't be needing you anymore. - Sidney!
- 你被解雇了 - 什么解雇
- You re fired. - Fired?
- 炒鱿鱼 - 行
- Fired! - Fine.
(医院主入口)
"你觉得我的书怎样呢 丽贝卡"
"What do you think about my book, Rebecca?"
西德尼从来没被解雇过
The problem of Sidney is she never gets laid.
甚至没吃过别人白眼
Or even a little shit faced once in a while.
9点她就会打电话来道歉 等着瞧
She'll call me at 9 to apologize. Just watch.
(出口)
她会找我的 给她一点时间
She'll come around. Gotta just give her time.
西德尼会...来的
Sidney will come....around.
我是丽贝卡
This is Rebecca.
我找西德尼·普雷斯科特
Sidney Prescott, please.
现在我负责普雷斯科特小姐的公关
I am handling Ms Prescott's calls and appearances.
可以为你留言吗
May I take a message?
你就是留言
You are the message.
记好了吗
Are you writing this down?
正记着 但我听不太清
Yes, I am. But, it's kinda hard to hear you.
我和西德尼在医院里
I'm in a hospital, with Sidney.
你可以稍等一下吗
If you can just hang on one second.
我能等 但是你就不能了
I've got time. It's you that doesn't.
丽贝卡 你那边听起来
You know, Rebecca, it doesn't sound to me
不太像医院啊
like you're in the hospital.
像是在停车场
Sounds like you re in a parking garage.
昏暗荒芜的停车场
A dark and deserted parking garage.
但是如果你想去医院
But if you wanna be in the hospital,
我很乐意送你去 太平间
I'd be happy to put you there. In the morgue!
救命 救命 救救我
Help! Help! Save me!
神出鬼没 你这个杂种
Cut and run, you fucking bastard.
(楼梯 六楼)
调查在进行中
This is an ongoing investigation.
毫无疑问 我们已有多条线索
But rest assured, we're pursuing a number of leads.
- 警长 - 我说的越少越好
- Sheriff. - The less I say about that, the better.
那到了答疑时间
So, I'm taking questions.
- 杜威 - 加尔
- Dewey! - Gale?
这几起谋杀似乎是模仿最初的
Any comment on the fact that these killings seem to resemble
伍兹伯勒杀人案 你有何看法
the pattern of the original Woodsboro murders?
什么 等会再说
Hun? Later!
那是什么意思 警长
What was that, Sheriff?
正如我所说的...警员们正在加紧破案
As I was saying...my officers are hard at work.
我们只希望公众了解
We just want the community to know
我们很快就能控制局面
that we're very close to bringing this whole situation under control.
(KQWK 第十三频道 海湾地区新闻)
快来人 到顶楼去看看 快去
Hey, someone! Get up to the top of the structure! Go! Go!
- 都退后 - 后退 都不许动
- Everyone back! Stay back! - Back, nobody move!
詹金斯 派人到楼梯井上看看
Jenkins, I want a man on this stairwell.
- 看见谁了吗 - 没人在那
- You see anybody? - Nobody out there.
那里没人 警长
There's nobody out there, Sheriff!
尽在掌控中吗 警长
It's all under control huh, Sheriff?
那我能怎么说
But what am I supposed to say?
听着 可能我不是警察
Listen, I may not be wearing a uniform,
但我刚好有一条你没有的线索
but I happen to have a lead and you don't.
想合作的时候通知我一声
So let me know when you're back on Team Gale.
后退 我是警长家的
Move back, I am the Sheriff.
(伍兹伯勒高中)
(放映俱乐部)
很好 伙计们 我们现在开讲
Ok, Cinema Club, we're now in session.
(刺杀)
(活死人黎明)
我们是一个被认可的学校团体
We're a sanctioned after school activity,
位于合唱团楼下
one rung below the Glee club,
任天堂游戏健身楼上两层
two above Nintendo Wii Fit
容我先向我们的特邀嘉宾致敬
and let me just say to our guest,
西德尼·普雷斯科特 非常荣幸
Sidney Prescott, it's an honor.
你的加入就是终极体验
I mean, this is the ultimate.
估计我该说谢谢
Thanks, I-I guess.
这...你把全部校园生活拍成电影
This, uhm...you film your entire High School experience
然后呢 传到网上吗
and what, post it on the net?
这早晚会成为一种趋势 西德
Everybody will be doing it someday, Sid.
这正是凶手所遗漏的
It's kind of the one component the killer is missing.
等等 什么意思
Wait, what do you mean?
要想成为新的"新版本"
Well, if you wanna be the new "New version",
凶手应该拍下谋杀过程
the killer should be filming the murders.
这是精神凌虐创新中很自然的一步
That's like the natural next step in the psycho slasher innovation.
也就是说 你实时拍下谋杀场景
I mean you film em all real time
然后在被抓前 上传到网上
and then before you get caught, you upload em into cyberspace.
让你的杰作与你一起永存
Making your art as immortal as you.
- 不是指他... - 不是指我...
- Not to implicate him... - Not to implicate me...
那你认为谁是凶手
So who do you think is behind the murders?
显然是个《刺杀》迷
Well, it's a Stab fanatic, clearly.
不太注重布景 更注重气氛
Working on less of a Screquel and more of a Screamake.
顺便一提 我们独创的词汇
Copyrighted terms, by the way.
因为现在这一切都是重演
Cos all there are now are remakes.
制片厂只给恐怖片放行
Only horror the studios green-light.
规则还在 只是已经变了
I mean, there are still rules, but the rules have changed.
新的陈腔滥调是不被允许的
The unexpected is the new cliche.
没错 你必须有惊人的开场白
Yeah, you gotta have an opening sequence that blows the doors off
配上超炫的音乐视频录制
done with some flashy music video direction.
杀戮就需要更加极端
And the kills gotta be way more extreme.
现在的观众对原来的规则很熟悉了
Modern audiences got savvy to the rules of the originals,
所以反其道而行成了新的规则
so the reversals become the new standard.
事实上 现在的恐怖片里你想活命
In fact, the only surefire way to survive
唯一的可能性就是 你是同性恋
a modern horror movie, you pretty much have to be gay.
那你如何确定凶手是在故事重现呢
So, why are you so sure that the killer is working by the rules of a horror remake?
电影《刺杀》的结构非常清晰
Well, the original Stab structure is pretty apparent.
父母外出时两个孩子在家里被杀
Two kids killed in a house while their parents are away.
之后校花被摧残得面目全非
And then the school's "Hot chick" savaged beyond recognition.
我们都知道下一次在哪里...
We all know where it goes from there...
派对上
A party.
正是 第三起肯定血流成河
Exactly. A party. Guaranteed third act main cast blood bath.
期待出现裸体美人
Fingers crossed on some nudity for a change.
你知道今晚的派对吗
Ok, do you know of a party that's happening tonight?
是有个刺杀之夜
Well, there's Stab-a-thon.
刺杀之夜
Stab-a-thon?
是一个电影循环放映
Uh, It's a movie marathon.
全七部《刺杀》连续播放
All 7 Stabs back to back.
每年都举行
We do it every year.
是今晚吗
Is tonight?
模仿原版电影的凶手还在逍遥法外
There's a killer out there patterning his murders after the original movie.
我知道 很疯狂吧
I know, it's pretty wild.
我们必须取消派对
We have to call it off.
我是说 今天是周五
Uhm, ok, I mean, it's Friday.
这肯定不是伍兹伯勒唯一的派对
I am sure we're not the only party that's going on at Woodsboro.
这个蠢派对在哪里举行
But where is this circle-jerk gonna take place?
那现在是提问时间
So, let's ready for this Q&A.
不 不 我要知道地址
No, no. I really want the location.
这是秘密集会
You know, it's kind of an underground thing.
通过邮件邀请 非常隐秘
Email invites. Pretty secret.
那么你不打算告诉我了
What, you're not gonna tell me?
真的 我们是搭档 忘了吗
Really? We're working together. Remember?
- 那开始提问吧 - 去你的 我们走
- So you're ready for the Q&A? - Fuck you. Let's go.
酷毙了
That was awesome.
- 未经允许谁也不准靠近屋子 - 明白
- Nobody comes to the house unless we say so. - Got it.
感觉我被软禁一样
I feel like I'm under house arrest.
你知道有人说"我了解你的感受"
You know when people say "I know how you feel",
可你知道他们只是说说而已
but you know they're just saying that
因为他们根本就不懂
because they really have no freaking idea how you feel?
我了解你的感受
I know how you feel.
奥利维亚的事我感到很难过
I am so sorry about Olivia.
你公关的事我也很难过
I am sorry about your publicist.
大家一直盯着你 你怎么受得了
How do you handle it, people staring at you all the time?
大家有盯着我吗
People stare at me?
我觉得我永远应付不来
I could never handle that kind of attention.
我感觉那会颠覆你的全部生活
I just feel like it would take over your whole life.
我唯一做的就是...
Uh, all I do is I...
试着不去想自己
try not to think about me.
我有要关心的人 我关注他们
I have people I care about. I focus on them.
至于其他的 就顺其自然了
And the rest, uhm, it works out.
你昨晚救了我的命
You saved my life last night.
我知道我们是家人
I mean, I know we're family
可是...你察觉到我出事了
but... you heard a thing on me.
让我疑惑
Makes me wonder, you know,
自己是否有勇气做同样的事
if I'd be brave enough to do the same thing.
我真心希望你永远不必知道答案
I really hope you never have to find that out.
需要我的话 你知道去哪找我
Oh, if you need me, you know where to find me.
我就在我牢房里 我是说 房间里
I'll be up in my cell, oh, I mean, my room.
我们的房间被木板封上了
Our rooms are boarded up.
从我的小屋能看到 太奇怪了
That's the view from my cell. It's really weird.
我觉得奥利维亚会理解的 对吧
I think Olivia would understand, ok?
她也希望我出来散散心
She'd want me to be around other people.
真见鬼 我竟然到了蠢蛋聚集区
Holy shit. Even if I did just crash land on planet dork.
- 顺便一提 特雷弗在这里 - 科比
- Speaking of which, Trevor's here. - Hey, Kirby.
他在那干吗 这不像他的作风
What is he doing there? That is so not his scene.
我不知道 或许他以为你会来
I have no idea, maybe he thought you would be here.
是啊 太有可能了 经过昨晚的事
Yeah, fat chance. After what happened last night?
我妈完全吓坏了
I mean, my mum is just completely freaked out.
- 又不是第一次 - 好吧
- It's not prim. - Alright,
你当你的乖乖女
you go do your good girl thing
我会替你把你的那份酒喝了
and I'll drink for the both of us.
我会一直更新状态的
I will keep you posted.
好的 注意安全
Alright, be safe.
刺杀之夜
Stab-a-thon!
- 谢谢你们 谢谢 - 安静
- Thank you! Thank you. Gracias. Gracias. - Shhhh.
放映俱乐部感谢各位来参加
Cinema Club thanks you for
躁动派对3周年聚会
coming up for our third annual Stab-a-thon.
谢谢你们 参加3周年聚会的各位
Thank you, number-3-thon.
感谢你们光临
We thank you in rows.
准备好在手机没信号时
Are you ready to drink every time
- 痛饮了吗 - 是的
- someone can't get a cellphone signal? - Yeah!
准备好在关冰箱门时
Are you ready to drink every time someone shuts the refrigerator door and,
天哪 有人躲在门后时痛饮了吗
oh my God, there's the harmless character right behind it?
是的
Yeah!
你们准备好在有人大喊
Are you ready to drink
- 那个词时痛饮了吗... - 不要
- every time somebody screams the word.... - No!
让我们开始刺杀之夜
Let's get the Stab-a-thon started!
(刺杀)
鬼脸
Ghostface!
五秒内离开
Get out in 5!
快挪开
Move your ass!
给我滚蛋
Screw you!
(根据加尔·威瑟斯的《伍兹伯勒谋杀》改编)
搞定
Yes!
很好 我的好戏上场了
Uh, Yeah. Back on my game.
完美 新任务进行中 第一章
Perfect. New work in progress, chapter 1.
当我搬到伍兹伯勒时 我从未想过
When I moved to Woodsboro, I never in a million years dreamed
我会再次担负重任...
that I would again play the critical role...
解救另一群...
in solving another series of these...
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
加尔 你在哪
Gale, where are you?
我跟踪那帮孩子到了刺杀之夜
I followed the kids to the Stab-a-thon.
在迪伦四路的一个废旧农场里
There's an old abandoned farm on 4th Dylan Road.
听着 我放了监控器
Listen, I-I got it under surveillance,
但我认为凶手就要行动了
but I think the killer is about to make his move.
何以见得
What makes you so sure?
故事重演来超越经典
You do a remake to outdo the original,
这是那帮孩子说的
that's what the kids said.
这个派对的主题就是《刺杀》电影
This party is all about the Stab movies.
拜托 你还要多少证明
Come on, how meta can you get?
你说什么"什么"
How "What the.." Can you get?
我不清楚 我跟他们学的
I dunno, I heard em say it.
杜威 听我说 你得赶快过来
Dewey, listen to me, you have to get out here.
拜托 你抓凶手 我抢新闻
Come on, you catch the killer, I get the story.
双赢啊
It's a win-win.
我觉得你是太闲了 加尔
Well, I thought you were going rogue, Gale.
拜托...你是认真的吗 拜托
Oh come..Are you serious? C'mon!
算了 谢谢你对我的信任
Forget it. Thanks for having faith in me!
- 我要去修设备了 - 加尔
- I gotta fix my equipment. - Gale!
混蛋
Shit.
太棒了 干得不错 让我印象深刻
Bravo, well...very well done, very, I'm very impressed.
有点 挺不错 不见得
Kind of. Kinda impressed. Not Really.
那就足够了
That'll do.
- 够了吗 - 足够了
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- 没错 她想要你 - 是的 是的
- Yeah, she wants you. - Yeah. Yeah.
不要
Nooooooo!
鬼脸...
Ghostface...
- 你好吗 - 你好
- Hello? - Hello.
是谁
Who is this?
你在等谁吗
Were you expecting somebody now?
知道吗 虽然不知道你是谁...
You know, I don't even know you...
我已经开始讨厌你了
and I dislike you already.
希克斯 你离迪伦四路多远
Hicks, how far are you from 4th Dylan Road?
最多5分钟就能到 长官
5 minutes at the most, Sir.
快赶过去
Well, step on it.
看看窗外
Look out your window.
(一号摄像机 正在录制)
加尔 加尔 注意身后
Gale! Gale, behind you!
不要
No!
加尔
Gale!
不许动
Freeze!
快让开 你们这群蠢蛋
Get out of the way, you morons!
该死
Dammit.
- 用力按住 - 你抓住他了吗
- Ok, put pressure on that. - Did you catch him?
没有 希望你的监视器拍到些什么
No, hopefully your cameras got something.
不是只有我放了监视器 杜威
They weren't the only ones, Dewey.
- 什么 - 有个摄像头...在那边
- What? - There's a webcam... set back there.
- 他在观察我 - 摄像头吗
- He was watching me. - A webcam?
- 他在拍摄谋杀过程 - 什么
- He's recording the murders. - What?
这次...他要拍成电影
This time... he's making the movie.
这个西德尼·普雷斯科特推销员
This Sidney Prescott detail man,
我不喜欢
I don't like it.
监控房子的警察都明白
The cops scouting the house, they always get it.
- 你说什么呢 - 这是电影的警察规则
- What are you talking about? - It's a movie cop rule.
当电影里的警察糟透了
Sucks to be a cop in a movie.
除非你是布鲁斯·威利斯
Unless you're Bruce Willis.
不是所有电影里的警察都会死
Not all cops die in movies.
对 但如果你明天退休 你死定了
No, but if it's your last day before retirement you do.
如果是老婆怀孕了的新手 你死定了
If you're a rookie, some with a wife who's pregnant, you do.
或者要是你的搭档比你帅
Or if your partner is better looking than you,
你死定了 顺便一提 我比较帅
you do, and by the way, I win that one.
那么我去巡逻吧 一会回来
You know what, I'll take the next perimeter. I'll be right back.
糟糕
Shit.
我知道的 你不该那么说 对吧
I know this one, you're not supposed to say that, are you?
新时代 会有新规则
Eh, new decade, new rules.
如今 你可能回来后发现我死了
You know, these days, you might come back, find me dead.
两眼突出 舌头外伸 都有可能
Eyes gouged out, tongue sticking out. Could go either way.
- 我得学会这套 - 这回我去吧
- I gotta learn this shit. - Eh, I'll take this one.
霍斯 小心点
Hey, Hoss. Be careful.
我行事一向小心
I am always careful.
赴死之旅
Dead man walking.
铂金斯 你上次巡逻时有窗户开着吗
Perkins, was there a window open on your last perimeter check?
铂金斯 请回复 完毕
Perkins, come in. Over.
安东尼 铂金斯
Anthony? Perkins?
- 该死 - 你真该看看自己的脸 新手
- Dammit. - You should have seen the look on your face, rookie.
霍斯 搞什么
Hoss! What the fuck!
真见鬼...
Holy shit...
霍斯
Hoss!
去你的布鲁斯·威利斯
Fuck Bruce Willis!
抱歉 风铃放在这里
Sorry. The wind chimes were over here.
是我放的 我想把它修好 抱歉
It was me, I was trying to fix em, sorry.
我刚从商店回来
I am just back the store.
你去买东西了吗
Were you shopping?
去释放压力
A stress buster.
车里还有一袋东西 我马上回来
I got one more bag in the car. I'll be right back.
吉尔 能接下电话吗
Jill, you're gonna get that?
罗伯茨家
Roberts residence.
你是个幸存者 对吧 西德尼
You're a survivor, aren't you, Sidney?
你唯一会的就是:死里逃生
Your one and only skill: You survive.
我有个问题要问你
Well, I have one question for you.
当亲近你的人都死光了
What good did to be a survivor in
你这个幸存者是不是还感觉良好
this little drama if everyone close to you is dead?
- 你是谁 - 打开电视 看6频道
- Who are you? - Turn on the TV to channel 6.
你究竟是谁
Who the fuck are you?
开电视 看预告片吧
Turn it on. Watch the teaser.
今晚险些有人丧命 这次的受害者是
But it nearly turned deadly tonight, with the latest victim
伍兹伯勒警长的妻子...
of this attack being the wife of the Woodsboro Sheriff...
加尔·瑞利 原名加尔·威瑟斯
Gale Riley, AKA Gale Weathers, who's in serious
被严重刺伤 而袭击者...
condition tonight after being stabbed. Her assailant then disappeared...
- 趁乱逃逸... - 欢迎回家
- in a sea of identic.... - Glad you came home,
西德尼 值得吗
Sidney. Has it been worth it yet?
- 你为什么要这么做 - 朋友也行
- Why are you doing this? - Ah, friends count,
但是家人可以伤害你更深 对吧
but it's the family ties that cut deep. Am I right?
- 你什么意思 - 你最关心的那些人
- What do you mean? - The ones you care about most.
有谁能比家人呢
And what's closer than family?
- 血缘的羁绊 - 别这么做
- The bond of blood. - Don't.
你救不了他们 你只能眼睁睁地看着
You can't save them. All you can do is watch.
吉尔
Jill!
(- 我妈快把我逼疯了 过来接我 - 马上到)
- 凯特 - 西德
- Kate! - Sid?
- 她不在房间里 - 天哪
- She's not in her room. - Oh my God.
她去了科比家 你得给她打电话
She's gone at Kirby's. You gotta call her,
- 让她回来 - 好的
- get her back here. - Ok.
- 接电话 吉尔 - 请留言
- Come on, Jill! - Leave a message.
- 她没接 怎么了 - 凶手打电话来
- She's not picking up. What's going on? - The killer called,
他在跟踪我 他想先杀了我的家人
he's coming after me. But he wants my family first.
- 天哪 吉尔... - 我们去叫警察
- Oh God, Jill... - Let's get the cops.
- 警察不在那 - 什么
- The cops aren't there. - What?
我第一次进来的时候他们还在
They were there when I first came in,
- 但现在不在了 - 我们去科比家
- but they're not there now. - Let's get to Kirby's.
走正门
Out the front.
能从底下撑住门吗
Press up on the bottom. Can you?
我们快离开这里
Let's get out of here.
凯特 快点 凯特
Kate, come on! Kate!
告诉吉尔我很抱歉...
Tell Jill I am so sorry...
不 不 不...
No, no, no, no, shhhh...
凯特...
Kate...
希克斯 你在干什么
Hicks. What are you doing?
我刚看见有人在房子周边晃
I just saw somebody coming around the side of the house.
霍斯和铂金斯哪去了
Where are Hoss and Perkins?
无线电联络不到他们
I couldn't get em on the radio.
那是谁的血
Whose blood is that?
是...凯特的 我们刚被袭击
Is...Is Kate's, we were just attacked.
她死了
She's dead.
- 她在哪 - 正门那里
- Where is she? - The front door.
- 带我去 - 好的
- Show me. - Ok.
- 待在这 - 好的
- Stay here. - Ok.
我是希克斯副警长
This is Deputy Hicks.
罗伯茨家发生凶杀案
I've got a homicide at the Roberts residence.
霍斯和铂金斯失踪了
No sign of Perkins or Hoss.
收到 我们会试着定位他们
Copy that. We'll try to locate em.
很遗憾
I'm so sorry.
你会没事的 好吗 我发誓
You're gonna be fine, alright? I swear.
你不再独自一人 我们永远在一起
No more on your own. It's you and me, forever.
轻点
Easy.
- 杜威 - 什么事
- Dewey. - Yeah?
- 答应我一件事 - 任何事都答应
- Promise me something. - Anything.
抓住那个混蛋
Catch that motherfucker.
当然 我爱你
Absolutely. I love you.
我也爱你
I love you.
那里完全乱成一团了
It was chaos. Utter chaos.
我简直不能相信
I can't believe that.
伙计 警长的老婆
The Sheriff's wife, man.
告诉我们取消活动
She told us to cancel it
但我们没有 结果这样
and we didn't and now this?
我们该怎么办
What are we supposed to do?
罗比 冷静点 这说得通
Robbie, calm down. It makes sense.
这也是关于故事重演
This is about the reboots too.
它超越了原本的结局
They-they-they one up the original ending.
"伍兹伯勒谋杀"以派对收尾
"The Woodsboro murders" ended at a party,
那在改编中...
so in the remake...
派对就不是结局 新规则
The party is the false ending. New rules.
- 正是如此 - 好吧 别见怪
- Exactly. - Ok, no offense guys
我要放《刺杀7》了
but I'm gonna put in Stab 7.
太好了...
Yes...
没人能阻挠我的电影节
Nobody cancels my film festival.
我不想看那玩意
Wohaa, I don't wanna watch that.
至少不想在奥利维亚出事之后
Not after what happened to Olivia.
拜托 这是她的最爱
Oh, come on. It was her favorite.
- 科比 你有不少经典片 - 没错
- Oh, wow Kirby. You have some classics here. - Yep.
比如《阴风阵阵》《威尼斯疑魂》...
"Suspiria", "Don't look now"...
你知道的
You know it.
我绝对可以对答如流
I can trivia your ass under the table,
电影男孩
cinema boy.
是吗 谁首次扮演皮脸(电锯杀人狂主角)
Oh, yeah? Who played Leatherface first?
冈纳·汉森
Gunnar Hansen.
你感觉到了吗
Wow, did you feel that?
刚才我们之间的磁场
The charge that moved between us, then?
是我 我有超能力
Oh, that was me. I have powers.
太性感了...
So sexy...
真受不了你们 还玩什么对答游戏
You guys are unbelievable. You're playing fucking trivia games?
警察要来找我们了
The cops are gonna come for us,
他们会关掉我的网站
they are gonna shut down my website.
- 我们完蛋了 - 说得对
- We're so dead! - Yeah. I agree.
- 老天 你从哪冒出来的 - 正门
- Jesus Christ, where did you come from? - The front door.
顺便一提 科比
By the way Kirby,
根据目前的情况...
with everything that's going on right now...
- 你最好锁好门 - 抱歉...
- you probably shouldn't leave that unlocked. - Sorry...
还有...我能问一下你来干嘛吗
And...may I ask what the hell are you doing here?
为什么这么问 这不是余兴派对吗
Why, didn't I find the after-party?
不是 这是私人派对
No, you found the Anti-party
需要邀请
and it's invitation only.
吉尔邀请我了
Yeah, well, I got an invitation. From Jill.
- 是什么事啊 - 什么
- So, what's the story? - What?
你给我发了短信
You sent me a text message.
在科比家的余兴派对
After-party at Kirby's house.
我是说 你手机发我的
I mean, it was from your phone.
什么意思 从我的手机
What do you mean, from my phone?
我手机哪去了
Oh, where is my phone?
估计落在你车里了 我没给他发短信
I think I left it in your car, I didn't text him.
我没给你发短信 我会证明的
I didn't text you. And I'll prove it!
那么 查理 罗比
So, Charlie, Robbie,
促成犯罪的滋味如何呢
how does it feel to be accessories to a crime, huh?
- 真的吗 杜威的老婆 - 我完蛋了
- I mean, really? Dewey's wife? - My life is over.
到底你们谁用
So which one of you guys
吉尔的手机给我发的短信
sent me a text message from Jill's phone, huh?
我们是不是该相信
W...We're just supposed to accept that
你说的是真的呢
you're telling the truth?
你的手机不是丢了吗
Isn't your phone missing?
又买了个新的
Got a new one.
真的吗 真是神速啊
Really? Oh, that's incredibly convenient.
- 杜威 我是希克斯 - 什么事
- Dewey, it's Hicks. - What's up?
- 凯特·罗伯茨死了 - 什么
- Kate Roberts is dead. - Huh?
西德尼逃离了现场
And Sidney fled the scene.
什么 凯特怎么死的
What, what happened to Kate?
被刀捅死的 和其他人一样
She was stabbed, just like the others.
吉尔怎么样
And what about Jill?
还不清楚
No sign of her at all.
霍斯和铂金斯跑哪里去了
Where the hell were Hoss and Perkins?
他们在两街区外被发现死在车里
They were found dead in their car two blocks away.
身上多处刀伤
Multiple stab wounds.
- 好的 我马上就到 - 好的 长官
- Ok. I'm on my way. - Yes, Sir.
- 打错了 - 谁啊
- Wrong number. - Who was that?
- 没谁 - 电影选好了吗
- Oh, nobody. - Did you pick a movie?
是的 恐怖无比的《电锯4》
Yeah, we're gonna go scary: Saw IV.
我在电影院看过了 特烂
Oh, I saw that in theaters. It sucks.
一点都不可怕 特恶心
It's not scary, it's gross.
我痛恨一切变态低俗的玩意
I hate all that torture porn shit.
干嘛生气啊
Why, angry feel.
我喜欢竖锯(《电锯惊魂》主角)
Well, I like Jigsaw.
他杀人很有创意
I think he kills people very creatively.
但她才不在乎谁死了...
But she don't give a shit who dies...
因为里面从来就没有一个完整的角色
...cos there's no character to fill a man.
有的只是人被大卸八块 鲜血狂喷
It's just body parts whipping and blood spewing...
查理 愿意坐在我旁边吗
Charlie, you wanna sit next to me?
下一个是罗比·默塞尔的额外报道
Alright...Get ready for a Hall Pass with Robbie Mercer extra.
今晚 查理·沃克
Now tonight, there is a good chance that Charlie Walker,
对 就是我哥们 有可能交好运
yes, my Charlie Walker, may get lucky with a girl.
现在我不能泄露我的位置
Now I'm unable to, to publish my exact location,
可是 我敢肯定地说...
however, suffice it to say...
伍兹伯勒高中会有怪事发生
Woodsboro High may be in store for some geek history.
等着瞧吧
We'll see.
有人吗
Hello?
谁在那里
Who's there?
老天
Oh, my God.
你去哪里
Where are you going?
去看大门锁了没
To make sure the front door is locked.
- 不 别开门 - 你太敏感了
- No, don't open it. - You're overreacting.
- 查理 - 怎么了
- Hey, Charlie. - Yeah?
抱歉 我知道你正看得入迷
I'm sorry, I know you're into the movie and all ,
但...现在是行动的绝好机会
but...now would be a really good time to make a move.
叫我主动吗
For me to make a move?
- 你不能主动吗 - 我已经主动了
- Couldn't you make a move? - I just did.
因为你确实太可爱了
Cos you're actually pretty cute.
特别是当我害怕...
Especially when I'm scared...
孤独...醉酒的时候
and lonely...and drunk.
伙计们 看到吉尔进来了吗
Ehi, guys. Did...did you see Jill, coming?
我在外面没看见她
I didn't see her outside.
是的 特雷弗 她在楼上
Yes, Trevor. She is upstairs.
感谢上帝 你还想着保护她
Thank God you're here to protect her
甚至你都不知道她在哪
when you can't even find her.
- 外面没人 - 伙计
- There's nobody out here. - Oh, dude.
我超喜欢这段 对 对 对
I love this part of the movie. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- 他说什么 - 正当你以为
- What is it say? - Just when you
房子里很安全的时候
think they're all safe and comfortable in the house
鬼脸从天而降
Ghostface comes in and bang!
我打扰到你们了吗
Did I interrupt something for you?
不会吧
Shut the fuck up.
谁请你来了 特雷弗
Who invited you, Trevor?
好吧 当然不是你了 老天
Alright. Clearly not you. Wow.
我上楼了
I'm moving upstairs.
从我家里滚出去
Get out of my house!
我有点醉了
Ehi, ok, I'm a little drunk so,
别在网上责备我了
don't blame me on your Internet connection.
我们去看看查理怎么样了
Let's see what Charlie is up to, shall we?
或者特雷弗和吉尔间的趣事
Or the saga of Trevor and Jill...
伍兹伯勒高中的复杂故事
Oh, intrigue of Woodsboro High.
谁会把杀人玩得这么有戏剧性
Who needs to kill around with so much drama?
伙计...
Oh, man...
这就好多了
Yeah... That's better.
等等 不 你不能 不 有规则的
Wait, no!. You can't, you can't, there's rules.
我...我...我是同性恋 同性恋
I...I...I'm gay, I'm gay.
我是说 如果这有用...
I mean, if it helps...
总是有个倒霉的女孩
...some random girl who gets a
接到电话 然后必然被杀死
call that undoubtedly ends up getting her killed.
一切都在意料之中
It's all so predictable.
一切都在预料之中 没什么悬念
There's no element of surprise. You can see ev...
科比 我的手机在你房间里
Kirby! So, my phone was up in your room.
根本没有给特雷弗发短信
There was no text message sent to Trevor.
真是个大骗子
He is such a liar.
- 他在哪 - 什么意思
- Where is he? - What do you mean,
他在哪 他刚上楼找你了
where is he, he just went upstairs looking for you.
他不在楼上
He's not upstairs.
特雷弗
Trevor!
查理 罗比
Charlie! Robbie!
也许在外面
Maybe they are outside.
- 吉尔 - 西德尼
- Jill! - Sidney!
对不起
I am sorry,
我该告诉你和妈妈 我来这里
I should have told you and mom where I was going.
不 没关系 跟我走就好
No, it's ok, just I need you to come with me.
- 马上跟我走 好吗 - 罗伯
- Come with me right now, ok? - Rob.
罗比
Robbie!
快
Go!
西德尼
Sidney!
快啊
Come on!
- 阳台 - 没有别的路了吗
- The balcony! - There's no other way out?
我们可以跳下去
We can jump?
不能走老套路
It's two stories.
你手机呢 到床底下去
Where's your cell? Get under the bed.
- 什么 - 照我说的做
- What? - Just do what I say.
我来找你之前
And don't make a sound
待着别动别出声
and don't come out till I come get you.
- 快点 相信我 - 好
- Just go. Trust me! - Ok.
明白吗 好了吗 快跑 吉尔
You got it? You ok? Jill, run.
别停下 快跑
Just keep running. Get out!
- 你好 - 杜威
- Hello? - Dewey!
- 西德尼 你在哪 - 在科比家
- Sidney, where are you? - I'm at Kirby's.
凶手也在这 快来救我
The killer is here, I need your help.
- 马上就到 - 好
- I'm on my way. - Ok.
西德 西德尼
Sid! Sidney!
所有单位赶去维斯普巷道329号
I need all units to 329 Whispering Lane.
所有单位 维斯普巷道329号
All units! 329 Whispering Lane!
抱歉 是我 我试着
Sorry, it's just me. Look, I tried to call
用有线电话报警
911 with the land line instead,
但有人把路由器给砸烂了
but someone smashed the router.
- 我已经报警了 - 吉尔在哪
- I think I called them myself. - Well, where's Jill?
快 快 快 快
Go, go, go, go!
下面有个房间 我们可以藏在里面
There's a room down there. We can lock ourselves in.
我听见你大声叫吉尔
I heard you yelling to Jill.
- 她逃走了吗 - 我想她没事
- Did she get away? - I think she's safe.
科比 让我进去
Kirby, let me in!
查理...
Charlie...
不不不 我找到了罗比
No, no, no, no, no, don't. I just found Robbie.
这...这是他的血 拜托
It's...It's just his blood, please.
拜托 凶手就在外面
Please, there is someone else out here.
- 让我进去 - 不信任他 就别开门
- Let me in. - If you can't trust him, don't open the door.
天啊 让我进去
My God! Let me in!
离门远点 查理
Get away from the door, Charlie.
科比 是我啊 让我进去吧
Kirby, it's me! Please let me in!
离门远点 查理
Get away from the door, Charlie!
是我啊
It's me!
抱歉 我不能...
I'm sorry, I can't...
- 你他妈的搞什么... - 对不起
- What the fuck... - I am sorry.
你背后 小心
Behind you! Look out!
不不 不不不
No, no, no, no, no!
科比
Kirby!
不 天啊 不 快放了他
Oh, no, God, no. He's...Leave him alone!
放过他
Leave him alone!
是查理的手机
It's Charlie's phone.
告诉西德尼今晚将人头落地
Tell Sidney heads are gonna roll tonight.
告诉西德尼都是她的错
Tell Sidney it's all because of her.
或许她想和他一样
Or maybe she wants into his place.
- 我答应她做得利落些 - 是他
- I promise to be quick. - It's him.
好 我去找吉尔 她应该在老地方
Ok, I'm gonna get Jill, she should be in the same place.
尽量拖住他 我马上回来 好吗
Just-just keep him on the phone, I'll be right back ok?
放了他 求你...
Let him go, please...
我听说你喜欢恐怖电影
I hear you like horror movies,
科比 你会像喜欢他一样喜欢吗
Kirby. But do you like em so much as him?
别管《刺杀》了 你已经身临其境
Forget watching Stab. You get to live it.
不不不不 他才是专家 我不是
No, no, no, no, no. He's the expert, it's not me.
热身问题:詹森的凶器
Warm up question: Jason's weapon?
大砍刀
Uh, it's a machete.
对了 你看 你知道答案
There, you see? You do know the genre.
- 迈克尔·梅耶斯呢 - 屠刀
- Michael Mayers? - Uh, butcher knife.
- 皮面呢 - 电锯 求你了...
- Leatherface? - A chainsaw. Please...
你需要帮助的话就问西德尼
Just ask Sidney if you need some help.
- 弗莱迪·克鲁格呢 - 剪刀手
- Freddy Krueger? - Uh, uh, razor hands.
哪部电影掀起了暴力狂潮:
Name the movie that started the slasher craze:
《万圣节前夜》《德州电锯杀人狂》
Halloween, Texas Chainsaw Massacre,
《魔屋》还是《惊魂记》
The Last House on the Left Or Psycho?
- 《惊魂记》 - 都不是
- Psycho. - None of the above.
是《偷窥狂》
Peeping Tom.
1960年由迈克尔·鲍威尔执导
1960, directed by Michael Powell.
历史上第一次用凶手的视角
First movie to ever put the audience
- 来拍摄的电影 - 等等 不 不
- in the killer's POV. - Wait, wait. No, no, no, no.
拜托 再问一个问题 就一个
Please, just ask me one more question, just one more.
好吧 科比 这是你最后一次机会
Alright, Kirby. Then it's time for your last chance question.
说出一部
Name the remake of the
独创性恐怖电影的重现...
groundbreaking horror movie in which the villain...
《万圣节前夕》《德州电锯杀人狂》
Halloween, Texas Chainsaw,
《活死人黎明》《隔山有眼》
Dawn of the Dead, The Hills Have Eyes,
《鬼哭神嚎》《魔屋》
The Amityville Horror, The Last House on the Left
《黑色星期五》《猛鬼街》
Friday the 13th, A Nightmare on Elm Street,
《血腥情人节》《来电惊魂》
My Bloody Valentine, When a Stranger Calls,
《厄夜舞会》
Prom Night
《黑色圣诞节》
Black Christmas,
《恐怖蜡像馆》《迷雾》
House of Wax, The Fog,
《食人鱼》其中的一部 对吗 对吗
uh, Piranha. It's one of those, right? Right?!
我答对了 他妈的我对了
I got it right. I was fucking right!
吉尔
Jill?
我赢了 查理
I won, Charlie.
我他妈的赢了 赢了
I fucking won. I won.
他想问倒我 但我赢了
He tried to beat me, but I fucking won.
太好了...
It's so great...
等等 快好了 太紧了
Wait, I'm almost there. Just hang tight.
科比 我要开始行动了
Kirby? This is making a move.
4年同窗 你现在才看见我吗
4 years of classes together and you notice me now?
太晚了 你个烂婊子
You stupid bitch! It's too late!
别出声 我了解 我了解
Shh, shhhh, I know, I know.
没事 慢慢来
It's ok, take your time.
这不像电影里
Doesn't happen as fast
- 速战速决 甜心 - 查理...
- as it does in the movies, honey. - Charlie...
科比
Kirby?
你知道 当你看多了电影
You know, you learn the law
之后就会明白一个道理
when you watch the movies over and over.
所有的情节都是为了杀死你
All the plots are about trying to kill you.
- 吉尔在哪里 - 你以为
- Where's Jill? - Oh, you think
她会跑掉 你以为所有人都会没事吗
she's gonna get away? You think anyone gets away?
- 吉尔 - 你好 西德尼 吃惊吧
- Jill? - Hello, Sidney. Surprised?
看好了 亲爱的表姐
Watch this. This is the part when,
接下来录制要...结束了
dear cousin, the cameras...turn off.
- 查理 - 我要好好折磨她
- Charlie? - Want her taken care of.
我还有罗比被杀的超赞视频
Then I got great footage in my Robbie kill.
比珍妮和玛妮还有奥利维亚的都要精彩
Better than Jenny and Marnie or Olivia even.
好 我们剪辑一下等会上传
Good. We'll cut and upload it later.
把这些都嫁祸给特雷弗
Make it all traceable to Trevor.
说到这...
Speaking of which...
似曾相识是吗
Remind you of anything?
- 吉尔 求你 - 闭嘴 蠢货
- Jill, please... - Shut up! Dick.
我做的一切 都是跟你学的
Everything I learned, I learned from you.
西德尼 你明白吗 有个狗屎样的男友
You think you had a shitty boyfriend, Sidney?
干了你 又甩了你
Here's one that fucks you, dumps you and
但又没能让你出名
doesn't even make you famous.
你在说什么 吉尔 我真心爱过你
What the fuck, Jill, I loved you!
快闭上你的狗嘴
Shut the fuck up, already!
警察肯定想你拿着这枪
Sure those cops wanted you to have this,
吉尔 用来自卫
Jill. For your protection.
放下枪...
Put it dow...
- 求你了 - 你不该把他们都杀了
- Ehi, please. - Shouldn't have killed all those people,
特雷 更不该都录了像
Trev. Gone and put it on video even.
但这对我来说受益匪浅
But it means a lot that you did it for me.
你到底在胡扯些什么啊
What the fuck are you talking about?
我可不吃你那一套鬼把戏
I am NOT the girl you cheat on.
一切准备就绪
I've gone thru everything.
我们时间把握得很准
We're definitely good on timeline.
是啊 我们是绝配
Oh, yeah. We're perfect.
不不不 求求你
No, no, no. Please.
准备好第3幕了吗
Ready for act 3?
猜到了吗 西德尼
Have figured it out yet, Sidney?
根据故事重演的原则
Keeping it to our remake theme,
特雷弗是新一代的
Trevor is this generation's
比利·卢姆斯(西德尼前男友及凶手)
Billy Loomis
而我们是无辜的受害者:西德尼和兰迪
and we're the innocent victims: Sidney and Randy.
因为你 全世界将知道
See, with you, the world just heard
发生的一切 关于我们 他们会看到
about what happened but with us, they're gonna see it.
这会轰动全球
It's gonna be a worldwide sensation. And
人们都会看到这个视频
people gotta see this shit.
这比看书要强多了
It's not like anyone reads anymore.
我会名扬四海
I gonna know fame like you never even dreamed of.
两个少年幸存了下来
Last two teenagers standing.
这次兰迪终于得到了自己的女孩
This time Randy gets the girl.
你太神奇了 完美的受害者
You're amazing. And you're the perfect victim.
我真是太不可思议了 不是吗
I was so unbelievable today, wasn't I?
我撒了那么多谎
I mean, I told so many lies,
我几乎自己都要相信了
I actually started to believe them.
我真觉得自己是个天生的戏子
I really think that I was born for this.
你怎么能这样做
How could you do this?
你知道生在这种家庭的感受吗
Do you know what it was like growing up in this family?
作为你的亲人 听到的一直是
Related to you? I mean, all I ever heard was
西德尼这个 西德尼那个
Sidney this and Sidney that,
西德尼 西德尼 西德尼
and Sidney, Sidney, Sidney.
你总是该死的特殊
You were always so fucking special!
现在轮到我了
Well, now I am the special one.
你不会成功的 向来如此
You'll slip, they always do.
来吧 查理 让我们开始吧
Come on, Charlie. Let's go on with this.
你必须坚强 忍着点 知道吗
You have to be strong and hold still. Ok?
对对 老法子 就像比利和斯图
Yeah, yeah, old school, like Billy and Stu.
来吧 宝贝 加把劲 来吧
Come on, baby, get it up. Come on.
朝这捅 朝这捅 朝这捅 来吧
Shoulder me, shoulder me, shoulder me. Get it up!
很痛 我们不是这样排练的
It's hurts! Not the way we rehearsed it.
像你说的 查理 比利和斯图
You said it, Charlie: Billy and Stu.
特雷弗和你
Trevor and you.
什么才是媒体的最爱 宝贝
What the media really loves, baby,
唯一的幸存者
is a sole survivor.
你知道该是谁吧
Just ask you know who.
特雷弗是你的搭档
Trevor was your partner and you,
而你则是主谋
you were the idea man.
- 你连朋友都杀吗 - 我朋友吗
- Even your friends? - My friends?
你搞清楚没有
What world are you living in?
我不需要朋友 我需要粉丝
I don't need friends. I need fans.
还不明白吗
Don't you get it?!
杀你不是最终目的
This has never been about killing you.
我最终是要...成为你
It's about...becoming you.
为了该死的这个 我妈必须死
I mean, for fuck's sake, my own mother had to die,
现在又死了这么多 我忠实了原著
now great loss there, so I could stay true to the original.
很病态 是吗 可病态也是一种清醒
It's sick, right? Well sick is the new sane.
你有你的辉煌 现在我想要我的
You had your 15 minutes, now I want mine!
我应该做什么呢
I mean, what am I supposed to do?
上大学 毕业 工作吗
Go to college, grad school, work?
看看周围 我们都活在公众的目光下
Look around, we all live in public now,
活在网络世界
we're all on the Internet.
你认为人怎样才能出名
How do you think people become famous anymore?
你根本不需要去争取
You don't have to achieve anything.
你只需要等着机会找上你
You just gotta have fucked up shit happen to you.
所以你必须死 西德 这是规则
So, you do have to die Sid. Those are the rules.
新电影 新主题
New movie, new franchise.
主角只有一个 面对现实吧
There's only room for one lead and, let's face it,
你纯真的日子 已经结束了
your ingenue days, they are over.
别告诉我你没预料到今天
Don't tell me you didn't know this day would come.
妈的
Oh, fuck!
快快 我们进去
Come on! Let's move in!
- 去各处房间检查一下 - 遵命
- Check the rooms, both sides and upstairs. - Yes, Ma'm.
吉尔 能描述一下发生的事吗...
Jill can you give us a description...
看这里...吉尔...吉尔
Over here...Jill...Jill,
当英雄感觉如何...
How does it feel to be a hero?...
(伍兹伯勒社区医院)
吉尔 你活着 这是最重要的
Jill. You made it. That's all that matters.
没错 查理和特雷要杀我
True, Charlie and Trev tried to kill me.
我听说他们杀了我妈
And I heard they killed my mom. And
罗比和科比也死了
Robbie and Kirby too.
别想了 休息吧
Shhh. Just lay back. Try to rest.
你妻子还好吗...
Is...is your wife...
她没事 她很坚强
She's gonna be fine. She's tough.
如果我有一天想写书了
If I ever write a book one day I'd,
我想和她合作
I'd want her to write it with me.
我们的伤口都一样 这是天意
It'd be a good team with our matching wounds and all.
我们都是幸存者
We're survivors now.
我真希望西德尼也是
I just wish Sidney was too.
吉尔 他们还不确定
Jill, they're not sure yet.
还在抢救
It's still touch and go.
但现在她在加护病房
But she's in ICU and
他们认为她能挺过来
they think Sidney just might make it.
什么 我是说 我看见特雷弗杀了她
What? I mean, I saw Trevor kill her.
我们还不确定 她还在挣扎
Look, we don't know yet. But she's hanging on.
我...我...我想见她
I...I...I wanna see her.
她还没醒
She's not awake yet. And,
她可能会失忆
she may not remember anything.
可能需要你帮忙
You'll have to help her with that.
不着急 好好休息 好吗
All in time. Just get some rest now, ok?
她还好吗
She gonna be ok?
是 她很坚强
Yeah, she's a strong kid.
她没得选择
She's gonna have to be.
她还问了你的情况
She asked if you were ok.
她认为你们俩应该联手写书
She thinks you guys should write a book together.
伤口都一样
With your matching wounds.
怎么 她也是伤在肩膀吗
Why, she was stabbed in the shoulder?
她怎么知道我伤在哪里
How did she know I was too?
糟糕
Shit!
你就是死不了 是吗
You just won't die, will ya?
你到底是谁 他妈的
Who are you,
迈克尔·梅耶斯(《夺命狂奔》主角)吗
Michael fucking Mayers?
不 差远了你
Yeah, I don't think so.
他妈的还不死
Fucking die already!
伤口还痛不痛啊
How are those stitches?
西德尼
Sidney!
希克斯 赶快去西德尼·普雷斯科特的病房
Hicks, get to the Sidney Prescott's room
- 叫人手来 - 马上 长官
- and call for backup! - Be right up, Sir.
- 西德 西德 - 杜威
- Sid? Sid. - Dewey!
就这么结束吗 西德
Is this how it's gonna be, Sid? The ending of the
电影的结局应该在家里
movie was supposed to be at the house.
我是说 这个结局很傻
I mean, this is just...silly.
或许结局不一样了呢
Consider this an alternate ending.
你跑不掉的 吉尔
You're not gonna get out of this, Jill.
- 我当然会 - 杜威
- Of course I will. - Dewey?
西德...
Sid...
冷静点 等等 我们的书怎么办
Easy..Wait, wait. What about the book?
看来我只能一个人写了
Looks like I'll just have to write it myself.
天杀的
Goddammit!
别想着开枪
Don't even think about shooting
否则我会打爆杜威的头
or I'll blow Dewey's head off.
- 以为我不敢吗 把枪给我 - 照着做
- What, you think I won't do it? Give me your gun! - Do it.
你想逞英雄啊 把枪给我
You just had to be the hero, huh? Give me your gun.
怎么 你聋了吗 把枪...给我
What are you, deaf? Give me...your gun.
站起来 双手抱头
And get up. And keep your hands over your head.
劝你别做蠢事...
Don't do anything stupi...
别他妈的告诉我怎么做
Don't fucking tell me what to do.
- 老天... - 站起来 贱人
- Oh, God... - Now, get up bitch.
- 好的 - 起来 快点
- Ok. - Get up. Now!
过来
Come on.
我们走 赶快挪屁股出去
Let's go. Get your skinny ass out here.
好...
Ok...
我要打爆你的头
I'm gonna enjoy blowing your head off.
好 但是...
Ok, but can I just
我能留个遗言吗
have one final word?
什么 求我吗
What? Please?
不是...
No...
- 开始(除颤器术语) - 清除
- Clear. - Clear?
开始
Clear!
你忘了翻拍的首要原则 吉尔
You forgot the first rule of remakes, Jill.
原创惹不得
Don't fuck with the original.
- 上帝啊 杜威 - 谁打了我
- Oh my God, Dewey. - Uh, what hit me?
别问了
Don't ask.
还好吗
You ok?
她就在我后面来着
She was standing right behind me.
他们总是如此
They always are.
天啊...
Oh, God...
好枪法
Nice one.
希克斯 你没死啊
Hicks, you're alive?
防弹衣在身 护住了我的胸
Wear the vest, save your chest.
两名警员受伤
I got two officers down,
几名居民伤员 一个新的疑犯
several injuries and a new suspect.
医生哪去了 天杀的
We need a doctor, Goddammit!
我不了解你了 但我感觉好多了
I don't know about you, but I feel a whole lot better.
我们在伍兹伯勒社区医院现场直播
We're live at Woodsboro Community Hospital,
等待幸存者吉尔·罗伯茨首次发言
awaiting a first public statement from Jill Roberts, survivor.
这个幸存者现在
A survivor of what is now
被称为"伍兹伯勒屠杀发现者"...
being called "The Woodsboro Massacre reboot"...
她叫吉尔·罗伯茨
Jill Roberts is her name.
这个名字现在已全球闻名...
A name the whole world will now know...
一位孤胆英雄
...who single-handedly put a
阻止了这场21世纪伍兹伯勒大屠杀...
stop to this 21st century Woodsboro killing spree...
伍兹伯勒的吉尔·罗伯茨 今晚
Jill Roberts of Woodsboro, a girl who's lifted
牵动着我们所有人的心 一位美国英雄
all our spirits tonight. An American hero,
从电影里走了出来
right out of the movies.